the ARR data.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thanks.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
So we're not seeing any contribution. So it's not a part of our research.
So if you're looking for historical studies for liver, a drug-induced liver injury, enzyme
elevations, etc., then there is no contribution from the remabrutinib ARR because all we see
in the blinded data would be consistent with what one would see from having teraflunamide
in the study. So that gives us a high degree of confidence, given that all these patients
now are well past 3 months where normally you would see any liver injuries showed up.
So it gives us high degree of confidence that safety profile for remabrutinib is clean and
consistent with what we saw in the blood.
with what we've seen in CSU, in Sindhu, in the phase two HS study, in the phase two food allergy
study. So now, you know, we have a pretty large portfolio of studies that have indicated the
clean profile of remibrutinib, but no insights so far on ARR. And I think we'll obviously read
out the studies this summer and we'll see where we are. Thank you. Your next question comes from
the line of Thibaut Botherin from Morgan Stanley. Please go ahead. Thank you very much. So my
question is just on Rapsido. The previous communication was that we should see limited
sales in Q4 last year, Q1 this year, because of the free scripts before we see a step up in Q2.
And actually, we saw quite decent sales in the first two quarters. So I guess the question is,
how much stocking have we seen so far? And should we still expect a step up in Q2
as well?
As we bridge to paid scripts? And in general, if you could help us with the dynamic in terms of
bridge for the rest of the year? Yeah, absolutely. I would say first on
stocking, we've seen stocking levels that are, you know, in line with what we've seen
historically for brands. So I don't think there's a significant, anything that's out of
what we would expect from a stocking perspective. I think when you look at the early data,
as I mentioned, 6,000 patient starts, 3,000 prescribers, about a quarter,
of the top CSU physicians prescribing the medicine. So that's all, I think, the right
direction. We think that the early script data probably has to be interpreted carefully because
we are using sampling and bridge programs. And as payer coverage expands, we will start to see
the conversion from free to paid. But that's going to be a stepwise process over the course
of the year. We have some early access wins, ESI, Cigna, Optum. And, you know, we have,
we've been able to secure first-line post-antihistamine coverage across those commercial plans. So